you
We took the pieces from the fire
We pulled the diamonds from the wire
There was a time we had a name Before the fracture
and the flame Now all the colours bleed to white
Beneath this artificial light We are the
fractured prisons In the cold
We bend the light from stories we were told.
I shower glass to catch the morning sun. Look at
the beautiful damage we have done
They built a wall to keep us in They try to wash
away the sin Boo, every crack inside the stone is
just a path that we have known We hold the edges
sharp and clear There is no room for pity
We bend the light! We bend the light!
We ban the lights!
We are fractured prisms freezing cold We bend
the light from stories we were told
Let's share a glass to catch the morning sun Look
at the beautiful damage we have done
The Fractured Precepts